Eddie Woods papers, circa 1957-2009 M1386
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
- Series 4: Little Magazines
  - Apollo Helmet [James Scully]: 1983 (Box 20)
  - Are You A Kid? [Charles Plymell]: 1977 (Box 20)
  - Armchair Detective [O. Penzler, editor]: Vol. 17, No. 3, 1984 (Box 20)
  - Armchair Detective [O. Penzler, editor]: Vol. 18, No. 1, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Artbeat [San Francisco, Calif.]: March 1981 (Box 20)
  - Artfelt [United Kingdom, Geoff Clarke]: No. 6, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Artfelt [United Kingdom, Geoff Clarke]: No. 7, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Arts Liberation Front: 1985 (Box 20)
  - Artzien: Vol. 1, No. 8, 1979 (Box 20)
  - Artzien: Vol. 1, No. 10, 1979 (Box 20)
  - Artzien: Vol. 2, No. 1, 1979 (Box 20)
  - Artzien: Spring 1982 (Box 20)
  - Ascent of the Primal Eye [Joel Levin]: 1982 (Box 20)
  - Bananas [United Kingdom]: No. 1, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Bananas [United Kingdom]: No. 2, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Bananas [United Kingdom]: No. 3, 1975-1976? (Box 20)
  - Bananas [United Kingdom]: No. 4, 1976 (Box 20)
  - Bananas [United Kingdom]: No. 5, 1976 (Box 20)
  - Bananas [United Kingdom]: No. 6, 1976 (Box 20)
  - Bananas [United Kingdom]: No. 7, 1977 (Box 20)
  - Bananas [United Kingdom]: No. 8, 1977 (Box 20)
  - Bananas [United Kingdom]: No. 9, 1977 (Box 20)
  - Bananas [United Kingdom]: No. 10, 1978 (Box 20)
  - Barney: 1981 (Box 20)
  - Barney: No. 2, Winter 1982 (Box 20)
  - Barney: No. 4, Spring 1984 (Box 20)
  - Beat Scene [United Kingdom]: Issue 10 (Box 20)
  - Beatitude: No. 29, 1979 (Box 21)
  - Beatitude: No. 30, 1980 (Box 21)
  - Beatitude: No. 31, 1981 (Box 21)
  - Benzene [New York]: Vol. 1, No. 2, 1981 (Box 21)
  - Beschränkte Bewegung [Washington, D.C.]: 1983 (Box 21)
  - BEV: No. 1, 1988 (Flat-box 39)
  - Big River News [Calif.]: Vol. 10, No. 6, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Bikini Girl [New York]: No. 6 1980 (Box 21)
  - Bill Dupp Soho Detective: No. 1, 1980 (Box 21)
  - Birds of Prey [Joyce Mansour]: 1979 (Box 21)
  - Bit Rare [United Kingdom]: Bitman No. 15 (Box 21)
  - Bitch, Butch, Black & Bad: 1977 (Box 21)
  - Bittersweet [United Kingdom]: No. 14 (Box 21)
  - Blades: No. 15, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Blades: No. 16, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Blades: No. 17, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Black Dwarf: No. 3 (Box 21)
  - Blake Times [United States, Kush, editor]: No 1? (Box 21)
  - Blake Times [United States, Kush, editor]: No. 2 (Box 21)
  - Blank Like Me [H. Fisher]: 1980 (Box 21)
  - Boss [New York]: No. 5, 1979 (Box 21)
  - Brave & Beautiful Future [Ernest Mann]: 1982 (Box 21)
  - Bres: No. 71, 1978 (Box 21)
  - Bres: No. 86, 1981 (Box 21)
  - Bres: No. 113, 1985 (Box 21)
  - Bres: No. 115, 1985 (Box 21)
  - Bres: No. 116, 1986 (Box 21)
  - Breyten Bretenbach on Trial [Amsterdam]: May 1977 (Box 21)
  - Brother Spence [Che Wax] (a signed Che Wax collage is in Ephemera): 1979 (Box 21)
  - Brown Mills Review: Vol. 1, No. 1, 1980 (Box 21)
  - Brown Mills Review: Vol. 1, No. 2, 1980 (Box 21)
  - Bullshit [Lee Bridges]: 1973 (Box 21)
  - Call It Sleep [Cronin/Seltzer]: 1983 (Box 21)
  - Campaign Alice [Jim Quinn]: 1972 (Box 21)
  - Caravan of Dreams Theatre [Synergetic Press]: Vol. 1, 1983 (Box 22)
  - Caravan of Dreams Theatre [Synergetic Press]: Vol. 2, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Carsick [Plantenga]: 1977? (Box 22)
  - Catalyst [Washington]: June-July 1982 (Box 22)
  - Catalyst [Washington]: November-December 1982 (Box 22)
  - Catalyst [Washington]: Erotica Issue, 1982 (Box 22)
  - Chapel Perilous [Ken Weichel]: 1985 (Box 22)
  - The Charioteer [New York]: No. 20, 1978 (Box 22)
  - Chetana: No. 9, 1984 (Box 22)
  - Chetana: No. 11, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Chiron Review [Calif.]: Vol. 11, No. 2, 1992 (Box 22)
  - City Canticle [San Francisco, Calif.]: No. 2, 1981 (Box 22)
  - The Claim [Malcolm Bennett, United Kingdom/Netherlands]: 1983 (Box 22)
  - Clash [P. Aguila]: 1980 (Box 22)
  - Cloud House: No Date (Box 22)
  - The Coldspring Journal [Plymell]: No. 10, 1976 (Box 22)
  - Columbus Free Press [Ohio]: Vol. 13, No. 5, Issue 175, 1983 (Box 22)
  - Coming Attractions [Little Caesar]: 1980 (Box 22)
  - Concept: No. 2, 1994 (Box 22)
  - Concordance of High Monarchists of Ireland: 1982 (Box 22)
  - Contact II [New York]: Vol. 4, No. 20-21, 1981 (Box 22)
  - Country Decadence [Bill Butler]: 1971 (Box 22)
  - Cover [New York]: January 1988 (Flat-box 39)
  - Coyote's Journal [F. Beltrametti, editor]: No. 10, 1974 (Box 22)
  - Crisis Time: No Date (Box 22)
  - Cross-Cultural Review: No. 2, 1979 (Box 22)
  - Cross-Cultural Review: No. 3, 1979 (Box 22)
  - Crossing Border [Netherlands, Louis Behre, editor] (Music festival magazines): 1993 (Box 22)
  - Crossing Border [Netherlands, Louis Behre, editor] (Music festival magazines): 1993 (Box 22)
  - Culture of Narcolepsy [Plantenga / Haller]: 1982 (Box 22)
  - Daily Liar: 1962 (Box 22)
  - The Day London Was Invaded by Grass [Yankali]: 1979 (Box 22)
  - Dear Carolyn [A. and K. Knight, editors]: 1983 (Box 22)
  - Dear Little Prince [Hugo Manning] (One letter from Hugo Manning to EW is in the Miller, Henry file]: 1973 (Box 22)
  - Delaware Alternative Press: Vol. 5, No. 2, 1983 (Box 22)
  - Dimension [Austin, Texas]: Special Issue, 1978 (Box 22)
  - Dinner on the Lawn [Maryland, Doug Messerli]: 1979 (Box 23)
  - Directory of Alternative Communities in Great Britain & Eire: 1977 (Box 23)
  - Diversion: No.10 and companion volume, 1978 (Box 23)
  - Document [New York]: Vol. 1, No. 2, 1976? (Box 23)
  - Documents for New Poetry [University of California, San Diego, Ed Dorn]: No. 1, 1978 (Box 23)
  - Dogged Ripov [A. Russo]: 1982 (Box 23)
  - Dream Helmet [New Jersey]: No. 1, 1978 (Box 23)
  - Dremples: Summer 1975 (Box 23)
  - Dremples: No. 4, 1976 (Box 23)
  - Dremples: Nos. 5-6, 1977 (Box 23)
  - Dump Truck [Keith Abbot]: 1967 (Box 23)
  - Earth's Daughter [New York]: No. 18, 1983 (Box 23)
  - Eindeloos Amsterdam, Eindeloos Leven [Ferlinghetti Special]: 1981 (Box 23)
  - An Einen Freund: 1979 (Box 23)
  - Elephants [United Kingdom, Heathcote Williams]: No Date (Flat-box 39)
  - Emancipation [Washington, D.C.]: Vol. 6, Issue 3, No. 45, 1983 (Box 23)
  - Encyclopedia Psychedelica [United Kingdom]: Vol. 3, 1987 (Box 23)
  - Encyclopedia Psychedelica [United Kingdom]: Vol. 6, 1988 (Box 23)
  - English Abrasives [United Kingdom]: 1978 (Box 23)
  - Erotic Haiku [Ontario]: 1983 (Box 23)
  - Erotomania [Bill Wolak]: 1978 (Box 23)
  - Escape as Jet [United Kingdom]: No. 3, 1979 (Box 23)
  - Escaped as a Bird [Leprosy Mission]: 1970 (Box 23)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: Vol. 1, Nos. 8-9, 1983 (Box 23)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: Vol. 2, Nos. 5-7, 1984 (Box 23)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: Vol. 3, Nos. 11-12, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: Vol. 4, Nos. 3-4, 1986 (Box 23)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: Vol. 5, Nos. 6-8, 1987 (Box 23)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: Vol. 5, Nos. 9-12, 1987 (Box 23)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: Vol. 6, Nos. 1-4, 1988 (Box 23)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: Vol. 6, Nos. 5-10, 1988 (Box 23)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: Vol. 6, Nos. 10-12, 1988 (Box 23)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: Vol. 7, Nos. 1-5, 1989 (Box 23)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: Vol. 7, Nos. 6-9, 1989 (Box 23)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: Vol. 7, No. 10-12, 1989 (Box 23)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: Vol. 8, Nos. 1-4, 1990 (Box 23)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: Vol. 8, Nos. 5-9, 1990 (Box 23)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: Vol. 9, Nos. 1-4, 1991 (Box 23)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 33, 1991 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 34, 1992 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 35, 1992 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 36, 1992 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 37, 1992 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 38, 1992 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 39, 1992 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 40, 1993 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 41, 1993 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 42, 1993 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 43, 1993 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 44, 1993 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 45, 1994 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 46, 1994 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 47, 1994 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 48, 1994 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 49, 1994 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 50, 1994/95 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: Index, 1983 – 1994 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 52, 1995 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 53, 1995 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 54, 1995 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 55, 1995 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 56, 1996 (Box 24)
  - Exquisite Corpse [A. Codrescu, editor]: No. 57, 1996 (Box 24)
  - FagRag [Maryland]: Issue 41, 1984 (Box 25)
  - Fanatic [United Kingdom]: No. 5 (Box 25)
  - Feng Shui [E. Eitel]: 1984 (Box 25)
  - Fiction Monthly [San Francisco, Calif.]: Vol. 1, No. 5, 1984 (Box 25)
  - Fiction Monthly [San Francisco, Calif.]: Vol. 1, No. 6, 1984 (Box 25)
  - File [Toronto]: Vol. 4, No 2, 1979 (Flat-box 39)
  - FIP News [Monthly Journal of the Federation of Indian Publishers]: Vol. 5, No. 5, 1983 (Box 25)
  - The First Mayday [Voltairine de Cleyre]: 1980 (Box 25)
  - The First Poem [Lee Harwood]: Unicorn Poem Card 3, June 1971 (Box 25)
  - Flash Card [Joyce Mansour]: 1978 (Box 25)
  - Folklore Anthropology [E.P. Thompson]: 1979 (Box 25)
  - Footloose [Irving Stettner]: 1981 (Box 25)
  - For Artists With Ego Problems (flip book) [San Francisco, Calif.]: 1980 (Box 25)
  - Frammis [San Francisco, Calif.]: 1979 (Box 25)
  - Free Classifieds [United Kingdom, Geoff Clarke]: No. 1, 1982 (Box 25)
  - Free Classifieds [United Kingdom, Geoff Clarke]: No. 5, 1982 (Box 25)
  - Free Classifieds [United Kingdom, Geoff Clarke]: No. 6, 1983 (Box 25)
  - Future Tense [F. Kinsman]: 1980 (Box 25)
  - Gap of Dunloe [Joe Mellen]: 1978 (Box 25)
  - Garden of Ruin [M. Valentine]: 1980 (Box 25)
  - Gargoyle [R. Peabody, editor]: No. 19, 1982 (Box 25)
  - Gasolin [Germany]: No. 7 (Box 25)
  - Gay Sunshine [Calif., Winston Leyland, editor]: No. 14, 1972 (Box 25)
  - Gay Sunshine [Calif., Winston Leyland, editor]: No. 15, 1972 (Box 25)
  - Gay Sunshine [Calif., Winston Leyland, editor]: No. 16, 1973 (Box 25)
  - Gay Sunshine [Calif., Winston Leyland, editor]: No. 17, 1973 (Box 25)
  - Gay Sunshine [Calif., Winston Leyland, editor]: No. 18, 1973 (Box 25)
  - Gay Sunshine [Calif., Winston Leyland, editor]: No. 19, 1973 (Box 25)
  - Gay Sunshine [Calif., Winston Leyland, editor]: No. 20, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Gay Sunshine [Calif., Winston Leyland, editor]: Nos. 42-43, 1980 (Box 25)
  - Gay Sunshine [Calif., Winston Leyland, editor]: Nos. 44-45, 1980 (Box 25)
  - Gazunda [United Kingdom]: No. 3 (Box 25)
  - Gedichten [Diana Groenveld]: 1978 (Box 25)
  - Gentle Art of Camouflage [Fetish Books]: 1980? (Box 25)
  - German Guerilla [Cienfuegos Press]: 1981 (Box 25)
  - Het Gewicht: No. 2, 1978 (Flat-box 39)
  - Global Tapestry [United Kingdom]: No. 10, 1981 (Box 25)
  - Global Tapestry [United Kingdom]: No. 15, 1984 (Box 25)
  - God Nederland & Oranje: No. 7, 1967 (Box 25)
  - God Nederland & Oranje: No. 9, 1967 (Box 25)
  - God Nederland & Oranje: No. 10, 1968 (Box 25)
  - Gott Mit Uns: No Date (Box 25)
  - Hands on a Mirror [F.A. Nettlebeck]: 1987 (Box 26)
  - Harbinger [South Carolina]: Issue 5 (Box 26)
  - Hawk [Donna Simons]: 1976 (Box 26)
  - Heaven's Back Door [Germany]: 1980 (Box 26)
  - Helen Review [New York]: Vol. 1, No. 3, 1970 (Box 26)
  - Heretic Visions [United Kingdom]: 1981? (Box 26)
  - Hidebound Rimes [Jim Holmes]: 1978 (Box 26)
  - Holy Flip [Germany, Laufi, editor]: No. 4 (Box 26)
  - Holy Flip [Germany, Laufi, editor]: No. 5 (Box 26)
  - Home Planet News [New York]: Vol. 1, No. 2, 1979 (Box 26)
  - Hot Gossip: No. 2 (Box 26)
  - Hot Gossip: No Date (Box 26)
  - Hurrah [I. Stettner]: 1980 (Box 26)
  - Ideodromio (Greek zine)[Greece]:1980 (Box 26)
  - Identity [Toronto]: No. 1, 1981 (Box 26)
  - Identity [Toronto]: No. 2, 1982 (Box 26)
  - Identity [Toronto]: No 3, 1982 (Box 26)
  - Identity [Toronto]: Nos. 4-5, 1982 (Box 26)
  - Idols [Dennis Cooper]: 1979 (Box 26)
  - Imagines [Seattle]: 2000 (Box 26)
  - In the Absence of a Surface [L. Beausoleil]: 1985 (Box 26)
  - In La-La Land We Trust [R. Campbell]: 1986 (Box 26)
  - In Naam van Mijzelf: No. 11, 1978 (Box 26)
  - In Sessie: 1980 (Box 26)
  - Index on Censorship: Vol. 5, No. 3, 1976 (Box 26)
  - India Today [New Delhi]: Vol. 15, No. 12, 1990 (Box 26)
  - Inkblot [Theo Green, editor]: No. 1, 1983 (Box 26)
  - Inkblot [Theo Green, editor]: No. 2, 1983 (Box 26)
  - Inkblot [Theo Green, editor]: No. 4, 1985 (Box 26)
  - Inkblot [Theo Green, editor]: No. 9, 1988 (Box 26)
  - Inklings [United Kingdom]: No. 1, 1977 (Box 26)
  - Inside Out [Hanuman]: 1976 (Box 26)
  - Interstate [Texas]: No. 14, 1981 (Box 26)
  - Inter/View [New York]: Vol. 1, No. 2, 1969 (Box 27)
  - Invention of Style [D. Pell]: 1978 (Box 27)
  - Iron [United Kingdom; Peter Mortimer, editor] (See also Series 3: Special Books and Magazines): No. 29, 1980 (Box 27)
  - Iron [United Kingdom; Peter Mortimer, editor] (See also Series 3: Special Books and Magazines): No. 30, 1980 (Box 27)
  - Iron [United Kingdom; Peter Mortimer, editor] (See also Series 3: Special Books and Magazines): No. 31, 1981 (Box 27)
  - Iron [United Kingdom; Peter Mortimer, editor] (See also Series 3: Special Books and Magazines): No. 33, 1981 (Box 27)
  - Iron [United Kingdom; Peter Mortimer, editor] (See also Series 3: Special Books and Magazines): No. 34, 1982 (Box 27)
  - Iron [United Kingdom; Peter Mortimer, editor] (See also Series 3: Special Books and Magazines): No. 35, 1982 (Box 27)
  - Iron [United Kingdom; Peter Mortimer, editor] (See also Series 3: Special Books and Magazines): No. 37, 1982 (Box 27)
  - Iron [United Kingdom; Peter Mortimer, editor] (See also Series 3: Special Books and Magazines): No. 38, 1982-1983 (Box 27)
  - Iron [United Kingdom; Peter Mortimer, editor] (See also Series 3: Special Books and Magazines): No. 39, 1983 (Box 27)
  - Iron [United Kingdom; Peter Mortimer, editor] (See also Series 3: Special Books and Magazines): No. 40, 1983 (Box 27)
  - Iron [United Kingdom; Peter Mortimer, editor] (See also Series 3: Special Books and Magazines): No. 41, 1983 (Box 27)
  - Iron [United Kingdom; Peter Mortimer, editor] (See also Series 3: Special Books and Magazines): No. 42, 1984 (Box 27)
  - Jáma Revue [Prague]: Summer 1995 (Box 27)
  - January [Paul Kahn]: 1978 (Box 27)
  - Jutta [Judy Semon]: 1978 (Box 27)
  - Kaguya Hime [Aikiku]: 1980 (Box 27)
  - Kenyon Review: Vol. 1, No. 3, 1979 (Box 27)
  - Kerwin: The Poem: 1984 (Box 27)
  - Kick it Over [Toronto]: No. 15, 1986 (Box 27)
  - Kick it Over [Toronto]: No.16, 1986 (Box 27)
  - The Kid [M. Gimpel]: 1979 (Box 27)
  - Koecrandt (Diana (then Gretchen) Ozon was involved with this): No. 43, 1980 (Box 27)
  - Komm-Zeitung [Germany]: No. 6, 1979 (Box 27)
  - Kreeft-keerkring [Cafe Miller publication]: 1993? (Box 27)
  - LANGUAGE [New York]: No. 6, 1978 (Box 27)
  - LANGUAGE [New York]: No. 11, 1980 (Box 27)
  - Legumes [Calif.]: Vol. 1, No. 1, 1981 (Box 27)
  - Leonardo Was Right [Roland Topor]: 1978 (Box 27)
  - Letters [Trantino]: 1971? (Box 27)
  - Letters Home [M. Andre]: 1979 (Box 27)
  - Letters to Jodie [John Hinckley]: 1981? (Box 27)
  - Letting You Know [Akiku]: 1979 (Box 27)
  - Libertine [United Kingdom]: No. 6 (Box 28)
  - Libertine [United Kingdom]: No 7 (Box 28)
  - Libertine [United Kingdom]: No 8 (Box 28)
  - Libertine [United Kingdom]: No 11 (Box 28)
  - Libertine [United Kingdom]: No 12 (Box 28)
  - Libertine [United Kingdom]: No 13 (Box 28)
  - Libertine [United Kingdom]: No 14 (Box 28)
  - Libertine [United Kingdom]: No 16 (Box 28)
  - Libertine [United Kingdom]: No 18 (Box 28)
  - Libertine [United Kingdom]: No 19 (Box 28)
  - Libertine [United Kingdom]: No 20 (Box 28)
  - Libertine [United Kingdom]: 2 issues, No Date (covers torn off) (Box 28)
  - Lichtspuren [Germany, Bernard Streit, editor]: No. 3, 1981 (Box 28)
  - Lichtspuren [Germany, Bernard Streit, editor]: No. 4, 1981 (Box 28)
  - Lichtspuren [Germany, Bernard Streit, editor]: No. 5, No Date (Box 28)
  - Lichtspuren [Germany, Bernard Streit, editor]: Christoph Derschau, 1982 (Box 28)
  - Lichtspuren [Germany, Bernard Streit, editor]: Matthyas Jenny, 1983 (Box 28)
  - Lichtspuren [Germany, Bernard Streit, editor]: Jürgen Ploog, 1983 (Box 28)
  - Lichtspuren [Germany, Bernard Streit, editor]: Flugschrift, No Date (Box 28)
  - Lieve Vera: 1978 (Box 28)
  - Lightworks [Ann Arbor, Michigan; Charlton Burch, editor]: No. 5, 1976 (Box 28)
  - Lightworks [Ann Arbor, Michigan; Charlton Burch, editor]: No. 6, 1977 (Box 28)
  - Lightworks [Ann Arbor, Michigan; Charlton Burch, editor]: No. 10, 1978 (Box 28)
  - Lightworks [Ann Arbor, Michigan; Charlton Burch, editor]: Nos. 11-12, 1979 (Box 28)
  - Lightworks [Ann Arbor, Michigan; Charlton Burch, editor]: No. 13, 1980 (Box 28)
  - La Ligna: No. 2, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Listen to the Mockingbird [Tuli Kupferberg]: 1980 (Box 28)
  - Little Caesar [United States; Dennis Cooper, editor]: Vol. 1, No. 1, 1976 (Box 28)
  - Little Caesar [United States; Dennis Cooper, editor]: No. 10, 1980 (Box 28)
  - Little Caesar [United States; Dennis Cooper, editor]: No. 11, 1980 (Box 28)
  - Little History of Bladud [United Kingdom]: 1973 (Box 28)
  - Little Review [West Virginia]: Vol. 6, Nos. 1-2, Issues 13-14 (Box 28)
  - Little Review [West Virginia]: Vol. 7, No. 1, Issue 15 (Box 28)
  - Live Oaks Leaves [San Francisco, Calif.]: Vol. 1, No. 1, 1980 (Box 28)
  - The Living Color [Calif.]: March-April 1982 (Box 28)
  - Local Color [M. Gottlieb]: 1978 (Box 28)
  - Logic of Snowflakes [H.D. Moe]: January 1979 (Box 28)
  - Long News [New Jersey]: No. 3, 1992 (Box 28)
  - Love Letter Hack [Michael Brondoli]: 1979 (Box 28)
  - Love Poems of Honniker Winkley [P. Silin]: 1978 (Box 28)
  - Lover John [Emanuel Po]: 1978 (Box 29)
  - Lucifer [Luc Sala] (Luc Sala published EW’s The Faerie Princess): No. 1, 1994 (Box 29)
  - Ludd's Mill [United Kingdom, Andrew Darlington, editor]: No. 12 (Box 29)
  - Ludd's Mill [United Kingdom, Andrew Darlington, editor]: No. 13 (Box 29)
  - Ludd's Mill [United Kingdom, Andrew Darlington, editor]: No. 13 (Box 29)
  - Ludd's Mill [United Kingdom, Andrew Darlington, editor]: No. 16-17 (Box 29)
  - Ludd's Mill [United Kingdom, Andrew Darlington, editor]: No. 18 (Box 29)
  - Lyrical Holland: 1954 (Box 29)
  - Magazine [Calif.]: Vol. 12, No. 3, 1982 (Box 29)
  - Maitri [Cape Town]: No. 12, 1982 (Box 29)
  - Making of an Anarchist [Voltairine de Cleyre]: 1978 (Box 29)
  - Mandala: No. 7, 1977 (Box 29)
  - Mantis [New York]: Issue 1, 1976 (Box 29)
  - Marijuana & the Bible [Florida]: No Date (Box 29)
  - Mars [United Kingdom]: No. 2 (Box 29)
  - Marxism & a Free Society [Marcus Graham]: 1981 (Box 29)
  - Matière [France; Gerrit Achterberg]: 1952 (Box 29)
  - May Day Speech [Jean Genet]: 1970 (Box 29)
  - Me & Big Joe [Michael Bloomfield]: 1980 (Box 29)
  - Mensenvlees Eten [Giorno]: Mandala-Extra, No. 2, 1976 (Box 29)
  - The Merry Muses [City Lights]: 1962 (Box 29)
  - Middel Klas Zes Gedichten [A. Piromalli]: 1977 (Box 29)
  - Midnight Extra [Diana Dreun (Doing!)]: No Date (Box 29)
  - Midnight Ink [United Kingdom]: Vol. 1, Issue 1, 1996 (Box 29)
  - Mill Hunk Herald [Pennsylvania]: Fall 1982 (Box 29)
  - Modest Proposal [J. Swift]: No Date (Box 29)
  - Momotaro [Peachuboyo] [United Kingdom, Aikiku]: 1980 (Box 29)
  - Monocle [New York]: Vol. 5, No. 3, 1963-1964 (Box 29)
  - The Monthly [San Francisco, Calif.]: Vol. 2, No. 1, 1981 (Box 29)
  - Moody Street Irregulars / Kerouac [New York]: No. 1, 1978 (Box 29)
  - Moody Street Irregulars / Kerouac [New York]: No. 2, 1978 (Box 29)
  - Moody Street Irregulars / Kerouac [New York]: No. 3, 1979 (Box 29)
  - Moody Street Irregulars / Kerouac [New York]: No. 4, 1979 (Box 29)
  - Moody Street Irregulars / Kerouac [New York]: No. 5, 1979 (Box 29)
  - Moody Street Irregulars / Kerouac [New York]: Nos. 6-7, 1980 (Box 29)
  - Moody Street Irregulars / Kerouac [New York]: No. 8, 1980 (Box 29)
  - Moody Street Irregulars / Kerouac [New York]: No. 9, 1981 (Box 29)
  - Moody Street Irregulars / Kerouac [New York]: No. 12, 1982 (Box 29)
  - Moody Street Irregulars / Kerouac [New York]: No. 13, 1983 (Box 29)
  - Moody Street Irregulars / Kerouac [New York]: No. 14, 1984 (Box 29)
  - Moody Street Irregulars / Kerouac [New York]: No. 15, 1985 (Box 29)
  - Moody Street Irregulars / Kerouac [New York]: Nos. 16-17, 1986 (Box 29)
  - Motherlode [Iris Berman]: 1983 (Box 29)
  - Moxa: 1978 (Box 29)
  - Murder Can Be Fun [San Francisco, Calif.]: No. 1 (Box 30)
  - Murder Can Be Fun [San Francisco, Calif.]: No. 2 (Box 30)
  - Murder Can Be Fun [San Francisco, Calif.]: No. 3 (Box 30)
  - Murder Can Be Fun [San Francisco, Calif.]: No. 4 (Box 30)
  - Murder Can Be Fun [San Francisco, Calif.]: No. 5 (Box 30)
  - Murder Can Be Fun [San Francisco, Calif.]: No. 6 (Box 30)
  - Murder Can Be Fun [San Francisco, Calif.]: No. 7 (Box 30)
  - Murder Can Be Fun [San Francisco, Calif.]: No. 8 (Box 30)
  - Murder Can Be Fun [San Francisco, Calif.]: 1988 (Box 30)
  - My Bijou [D. Miller / A. Fisher]: 1971 (Box 30)
  - My Regrets [M. Andre]: 1976 (Box 30)
  - My Summer Vacation [Charlie Walsh]: 1978 (Box 30)
  - My Tired Father [Gellu Naum, Inkblot]: 1986 (Box 30)
  - Narachan [Germany]: No. 5 (Flat-box 39)
  - Natural History [Geo. Myers]: 1981 (Box 30)
  - Negatism [United Kingdom]: 1983 (Box 30)
  - Nens, No Ninots [Spain]: 1978 (Box 30)
  - Neue Welle [Germany]: No. 3, 1978 (Box 30)
  - New Blood [Boulder, Colorado]: No. 1, 1981 (Box 30)
  - New Blood [Boulder, Colorado]: No. 3, 1981 (Box 30)
  - New Blood [Boulder, Colorado]: No. 4, 1981 (Box 30)
  - New Commercialist [San Francisco, Calif.]: No. 3, 1981 (Flat-box 39)
  - New Departures [United Kingdom, M. Horovitz, editor]: No. 12 (Box 30)
  - New Departures [United Kingdom, M. Horovitz, editor]: No. 13 (Box 30)
  - New Departures [United Kingdom, M. Horovitz, editor]: No 15, 1983 (Box 30)
  - New Instant [London]: No. 12, 1984 (Box 30)
  - New Instant [London]: 1985 (Box 30)
  - New Poetry [Australia]: Vol. 27, No. 3, 1979 (Box 30)
  - New Seed: Vol. 5, No. 8, 1976 (Box 30)
  - New Year's Greeting from Black Sparrow Press: 1982 (Box 30)
  - New Year's Greeting from Black Sparrow Press: 1984 (Box 30)
  - Nieuw Amsterdams Peil: No. 8, 1979 (Box 30)
  - Nieuw Amsterdams Peil: No. 9, 1979 (Box 30)
  - Nieuw Amsterdams Peil: No. 19, 1980 (Box 30)
  - Nips Poems [John Bennett]: 1980 (Box 30)
  - Northeast Rising Sun [Plymell]: Vol. 4, No. 16, 1979 (Box 30)
  - Northeast Rising Sun [Plymell]: Vol. 4, No. 17, 1980 (Box 30)
  - Northeast Rising Sun [Plymell]: Vol. 4, No. 18, 1980 (Box 30)
  - Northwest Passage [Washington]: Vol. 23, No. 7, 1983 (Box 30)
  - Not Guilty [D. Pell, editor]: Vol. 1, No. 4, 1979 (Box 30)
  - Not Guilty [D. Pell, editor]: Vol. 1, Nos. 5-6, 1980 (Box 30)
  - Nothing Nothing [Jeanne Lance]: 1979 (Box 30)
  - Oboe [San Francisco, Calif.]: No. 5, 1982 (Box 30)
  - Oculist Witnesses [Mass., Alan Davies, editor] (Includes Lewis McAdams and Gerard Malanga): No. 1, 1975 (Box 30)
  - Oculist Witnesses [Mass., Alan Davies, editor] (Includes Lewis McAdams and Gerard Malanga): No. 2, 1976 (Box 30)